Yusuf Wandana Web Developer

A web developer with 2+ years of work experience in analyzing, designing, developing, testing and maintaining web application systems and API services. I have built over 10+ projects during my time as a web developer.

Bogor, West Java, Indonesia +62 895 3756 37155 yusuf.wandana1@gmail.com itswandana.netlify.app

EXPERIENCES

PT. WAN Teknologi Internasional, Bogor

Web Developer

September 2021 - Present

- Analyze the client's desired application system flow.
- Design, develop, test, and maintain web application systems.
- Develop API services for web and mobile application developer needs on projects.
- Integrate applications with third-party services like payment gateway, PPOB system, SMS gateway, shipment service, etc.
- Collaborate with other teams on projects to achieve project target.
- Ensuring the codes is readable and easy to maintain.

PT. Madani Intelsysdata, Jakarta

ETL Developer

September 2020 - August 2021

- Develop reporting application for monthly financial report in a bank.
- Maintenance existing application, add new features and bug fixing.
- Become a consultant to assist finance companies in working on monthly financial report.
- Process data that will be used for financial reporting purposes using SQL Query

HARD SKILLS

HTML, CSS, JavaScript
Bootstrap, TailwindCSS
JQuery, AJAX
PHP (Laravel, Lumen)
Node Js (Express.js)
React Js
Golang
MySQL, PostgreeSQL
REST API
Git Version Control

SOFT SKILLS

Adaptable
Communicative
Critical thinking
Discipline
Fast learning
Problem solving
Hard work
Team work

EDUCATION

ITB Swadharma

Student of Computer Science 2022 - Present Bogor, West Java

SMK Wikrama Bogor

Software Engineering 2017 – 2020 Bogor, West Java